This is a tale from long ago.
Our kingdom of Highland was
once the land of the fairies.
The ferries were very
peaceful creatures. They
cherished all things
beautiful and fun.
So for hundreds of years they
enjoyed a tranquil existence.
But I feel so bad
for the fairies now. Yes.
It's very sad.
You see, 500 years ago,
humankind rose up
in rebellion and forced
the fairies to become
their servants.
Some people say
the fairies were fools,
that they idled away their time
and allowed the humans to win.
But mama doesn't believe
that's true at all.
The fact is that the humans
far outnumber the fairies.
So in a contest of strength,
the outcome was unavoidable.
How do you know that's
what happened? Just look. See?
Maybe.
Here.
His tasty sugar confections
are a sacred food.
It extends the lifespans of fairies and
brings good luck to humans,
and the first ones to create these
treats were the fairies themselves.
The fairies discovered the method of refining
sugar apples into silver sugar,
and we've been crafting all kinds of
confections from it ever since.
That's why silver sugar
masters and all sugar
artisans must never
look down on fairies.
We should co-exist
and treat them as
friends. You too. Anne? Yes.
Right.
Please watch over me, mama.
I'm going
to become a silver sugar master,
just like you were.
Here I go and wait. Huh? Please
don't leave yet. What? Jonas,
I can't believe you take
off without saying a word to me.
I'm sorry. I figured if I did,
you would try to stop me.
Oh,
I still came to stop you, Jonas.
I'm grateful to you
and your family.
They treated mama so well.
The entire village did.
But this is the year I'm
doing the sugar confectionery exhibition.
I can't sit it out.
Don't you see?
Sure I do.
I'm a sugar artisan, too.
But it isn't possible for you
to travel to Lewiston alone.
I mean,
you're so small for being 15.
You're scrawny as a scarecrow.
All you have
in the world
is that horse and cart.
But still.
I love you exactly as you are.
So will you please marry me?
I've told you before.
Ever since the day you
and your mother arrived here,
I've been completely
smitten with you.
I know that you feel empty,
but I will make you happy.
After all,
my family's quite wealthy. Akin
to the founder of the Radcliffe
Workshop School.
Huh? Anne! Come back! I'm
leaving. Jonas. But take care.
Anne, wait for me.
Please don't go. Huh?
Jonas would never seriously
propose to me. Of course.
He just pities me because
I lost mama.
That's a terrible reason.
But it's more than that.
I can't stand
the thought of being
married and devoting my life
to someone else.
I'd much rather live my own life
and chase my own dreams.
Right, mama?
You piece of trash!
How dare you!
Sorry. What's happening here? You're dead. I'll
squash you like a bug.
Oh, no. That man is a fairy
hunter who's punishing
his labor fairy.
Apparently, the creature took
its wing and tried to escape.
You sniveling little thief!
You think I
won't crush your wing
into pieces? No! Stop! Are.
More thing a. Swing is his life.
Why doesn't anyone help him?
It's because he's a fairy.
Of course.
Besides, that fairy hunter
is a violent man.
If you tried to intervene,
he might retaliate.
This is what you get
for defying me now.
Swear you never. Wait a minute.
Try to escape again.
I don't make promises to humans.
That's my wing,
you brute! I'll take
it if I want to.
All right, then.
I'll just have to destroy
you right here and now.
Excuse me, sir. Oh, and.
Here you go.
Hey, wait. What you want me.
To say thanks to a human,
I refuse?
Huh? Oh, right.
I suppose I am one
of those awful humans, aren't I?
That fairy was valuable.
And now it's
escape because of you.
So you owe me.
What do you care? I thought you
were getting ready
to murder him.
Either way, sir, you would
not have him anymore, huh?
Take it back.
Hey! That's enough!
A grown man like you
threatening a young girl.
Even if it was just a fairy,
there was no reason
to be that cruel to it.
That's true.
I'll remember this. Yeah. Get
out of here.
That was impressive. You're
putting your frail little
self in danger. For a fairy.
Though I look tiny,
I am actually 15 years old,
which means I can
care for myself.
My mistake. Ah, well,
you're a very kind soul.
Actually,
I wouldn't say that at all.
Would you tell me where
I can find the ferry market?
Trust me, these labor
fairies get the job done.
I've got some pretty ones.
Step right up,
rip off one of their wings,
and fairies
will do whatever you want.
Come look.
Would you happen to have
any warrior fairies?
Oh, I don't carry such
dangerous items as that.
The old man down
at the end has one,
but I wouldn't bother.
It's damaged goods. Thank you.
Beautiful.
That's an understatement. I've
never seen a fairy like him.
No, it's just a scarecrow.
Too bad. Scarecrow.
I mean, you who else?
Huh? Yes. You scarecrow!
Stop calling me that!
What a rude
thing to say to a young
lady in her prime.
You're wrong.
Scarecrows don't have a prime.
What? What's wrong with you?
Sorry about that.
Inventories got a little
bit of an attitude.
He spews insults at
anyone who passes
by, no matter who they are.
Don't take it personally,
why wouldn't I?
It's not my place
to give advice.
But at this rate, you'll never
sell him as a companion fairy.
Why don't you just release him?
Huh? That thing isn't a companion fairy.
It's a warrior type. Huh?
Three fairy hunters
died capturing him. That should
tell you what
an excellent article he is.
That can't be true.
All the warrior
fairies I've seen before were much bigger
and burlier than he is.
Fairy traders value trust.
Most of all, we don't lie.
Well, I did intend
to buy a warrior fairy.
But don't you have any others?
Warrior fairies are
difficult to handle. This
is the only one I have for sale.
You might want to look
elsewhere. Hey, Scarecrow.
You're not talking to me,
are you?
See any other scarecrows here?
Now stop
dallying and buy
me what did you say?
To buy you? Well,
this is quite a surprise.
I've never heard that mongrel directly order
a customer to buy him.
He must have fallen in love
with his girlie at first sight.
I'm not the same as you. Pardon?
I said that I'm not
the same as you.
You're nothing
but a filthy human. Ma, wait!
Ah!
Don't do that! You'll kill him!
Stop it! 100 crests are.
Will this be enough, sir?
A gold coin.
Now that's commitment.
You've made a wise purchase.
Here's his wing.
You can verify the goods.
So this is.
Precisely. It's my heart.
Remember to be careful, miss wore. Your
fairies are a dangerous lot.
Let your guard down even once,
and he'll
steal that leather pouch
and kill you in a heartbeat.
That isn't all. After she's
dead, I'll kill you. Just wait.
Hey, then I'll see you soon.
Come on.
Stop talking like it's
a sure thing that he's going.
To murder me.
Let's get out of here, huh?
Wait. Young miss,
are you certain that you'll
be able to make that ferry obey
you? Naturally.
Right, Scarecrow? It's an.
Anne Halford. Call me Scarecrow again, and
I'll knock your lights out.
I made it to Lewiston from here,
and I'd like you
to protect me along the way.
Can you do that?
Act as my bodyguard.
Easily, and I'll even throw
in a kiss as a bonus service.
Thank you.
But that won't be necessary.
Besides,
I don't want to waste me.
You haven't had your first kiss.
What a child.
Well, excuse me for being
a child. At least I'm not.
Look,
I don't even know your name.
Does it matter?
Well, I told you my name.
And I want to know
what I should call you.
Tom. Sam. Harry. Call me by any
meaningless human name you like.
All right then, Crow.
It is because
you're a scarecrow.
Consider it payback.
Shall find. Shall. Shall, shall.
Huh? That is a lovely name.
Which is the first
and which is the last?
It's just my name. We don't
differentiate the way humans do.
That makes sense. Shall find.
Shall is kind of long,
so I'll just call
you Shel for short.
Is that all right with you?
Like I said, call me what you
want.
You're my master, after all.
I guess that's true. Fairy's
wings are their very life force.
They can survive if
a wing is ripped off.
But if it's damaged,
we'll get weak and die.
When humans learned
that they started taking
one wing to force obedience. That's
how fairies became servants.
Listen, I bought you because
I need you to guard me.
But I promise you this.
After we make it to Lewiston,
I'll give you
your wing back to you.
Are you saying you're going
to set me free? That's right.
And waste the gold coin
that you spent on me.
And I didn't think a human could
be that naive. I'm not naive.
Well, it's just that I think humans
and fairies can be friends.
Is that so bad? I would
never want to control you,
but I don't want to sell
you to someone else either.
That's why I'll
return your wing. And while
you're accompanying me
on my travels,
I'd like to regard
you as a friend.
If you're all right with that.
Friends. That's impossible.
Mama and I used to dream. Then
we couldn't live in
harmony one day.
But if no one ever
takes the first step,
then that's never going
to be the reality.
So I want to make it possible.
Then she was brainless,
just like you are.
Don't you insult my mother.
Tell me. If you honestly
hate me that much,
then why did you order
me to purchase you?
I can't imagine
voluntarily working for someone
that I wasn't able to stand.
Human beings are all the same,
so I thought
I'd find myself a stupid one.
It's easier.
And in the last few years,
you might be the most
foolish human I've met by far.
The bloody highway is about
1200 Karen long.
There's not a single village or
town between here and Lewiston.
The only safe havens
are the fort shelters.
Convenient protection from wild animals and bandits,
of course. You've been here.
How many years do you think I've
been forced to serve humans?
Be thankful.
I know the way. Since you
bought me to be your escort.
Because you're a warrior fairy.
But. Okay.
Go ahead and start praying.
Reaching the first
fort shelter alive
won't be easy.
Hey, are you hungry? Mm.
Believe me,
I know we had good luck today,
but it's a long trip.
I'm counting on you
if the worst happens.
Huh?
He's difficult,
but fairy wings really
are pretty. May I touch it?
Huh? Don't touch me.
You may possess
my other wing,
but it's nothing more.
Sorry, I wasn't thinking.
Why did I
do that? I thought I understood.
Mama Ann, you're awake already?
You look upset, dear.
Did you get hurt? Huh?
No, I just had a bad dream.
You died, mama. It was awful.
Silly girl.
Focus on finding your life's
path and walk it
with confidence. Ah, mama.
I know you can do it.
You're a good girl.
Please don't cry, mom.
What's happening? You.
Huh? Was I?
Hey, what are you doing?
I don't understand,
why would you. Huh?
Your wing. Were you trying to
take it? I nearly had it, too.
How could you? I told you. What
about your friend?
And you're already betraying me.
My friend. When you're
holding my life in your hands.
You purchased me, remember?
You bet me to your
will. We can never be friends.
I'm being a fool, aren't I?
You're right. That was naive.
Even though I purchased
you to serve me,
I kept making selfish
requests to be your friend.
I won't let my guard down again.
A caterpillar now stick
with scarecrow. And I want
you to know that I'm going to
keep my promise no matter what.
After we reach Lewiston,
I fully intend
to give you your
ring back to you
and then ask one more time
if you and I can be friends.
Until then, I'm your master.
Understand?
I bungled that,
but there's no need to rush.
I've spent nearly 70 years
as a servant to humans.
My freedom may have to wait,
but in three days.
Again. Why does that scent
come from this girl?
The sweet smell of silver sugar.
Liz.
We need to get
to the shelter within the day.
We've traveled 200 Karen
on the highway.
That's only a sixth
of the distance. To stop here.
Find that magic.
Let's get them.
They're coming this way.
Wait a second. You're a warrior.
Fairy. You can get rid of them,
can't you? Too much work.
Serious? I am your master.
If you don't, they'll kill us.
What are you doing?
If you're my master,
why are you asking?
Just order me.
Come on now. Shouldn't you
go fight? You're blushing.
I'm begging you
to stop those bandits.
That didn't sound like an order.
If you
don't stop playing games,
we'll die.
Just say this.
Go slaughter those men
or I'll tear up your wing. Do I.
Have to?
Order me to. I said go
or else I'll punch you.
I suppose. That'll do.
As you wish, Lady Scarecrow.
Careful.
The guy is a damn warrior fairy.
Turn back now.